A Guide to the Register of Regulations records of the Virginia Code Commission, 1937-2021.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Register of Regulations records of the Virginia Code Commission,
1937-2021.
The Library of Virginia
43287, 50533, 51359, 51557, 51826, 51908, 51976, 52018, 52837, 53907
Virginia Code Commission
301 cu. ft.
Finding aid includes the the names of the agencies or boards included in each box. The provided links for for several accessions include a detailed folder listing for each box if one is available.
These records are part of the Virginia Code Commission record group (RG# 82)
Acquisition Information
Accession 43287 was transferred 06/29/2007
Accession 50533 was transferred 07/16/2012
Accession 51359 was transferred 07/14/2014
Accession 51557 was transferred 05/15/2015
Accession 51826 was transferred 06/14/2016
Accession 52018 was transferred 06/09/2017
Accession 52837 was transferred 09/25/2019
Accession 53907 was transferred 05/17/2023
Historical Information
The Commission on Code Recodification was created by an act of the General Assembly passed on March 30, 1946. Its principal duty was to make a complete recodification of the statute laws of the state of a general nature. This task was completed two years later, and the new code was approved by the General Assembly on March 30, 1948. An act passed by the General Assembly on March 16, 1948, made the commission a permanent agency of the legislative branch of government and changed the name of the commission to the Virginia Code Commission. The commission supervises the codification of the statutes after each General Assembly session and revises and recodifies portions of the Code of Virginia as needed.
In 1992 the Commission was charged with the responsibility of creating Virginia's first administrative code of regulations by compiling and codifying all of the administrative regulations of state agencies. The Commission also oversees the bi-weekly publication of The Virginia Register of Regulations, which is used by state agencies during the adoption of new regulations to be included in the Administrative Process Act.
Register of Regulation records, 1937-2021, of the Virginia Code Commission contain information relating to the development, review and approval of published and unpublished regulations that form the Virginia Administrative Code. The Virginia Administrative Code has the full force of law and is created by any state agency that is permitted to create regulations and must follow the procedures put forth in the Virginia Administrative Process Act. These records may include notices of intent, drafts of proposed regulations, economic impact analysis, request for comments, the final regulations, meeting notices, form, errata notices, documents both included and cited as precedent, emergency action material generated documents and other technical support material generated during the process to develop and approve the regulation.
Contents List
- Register of Regulations records, 1937-2021.
  - Accession 43287 (1964-1993, 8 cubic feet).
    - Dept. of Emergency Management, 1986-1993. (Box 1)
    - Dept. of Emergency Management / Dept. of Health - Hazardous Waste, 1976-1988. (Box 2)
    - Dept. of Emergency Management / Dept. of Health - Hazardous Waste, 1986-1992. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Emergency Management / Dept. of Health - Hazardous Waste, 1988-1992. (Box 4)
    - Dept. of Emergency Management / Dept. of Health - Hazardous Waste, 1990-1991. (Box 5)
    - Dept. of Emergency Management / Dept. of Health - Hazardous Waste, 1981-1989. (Box 6)
    - Dept. of Emergency Management / Dept. of Health - Hazardous Waste, 1992-1993. (Box 7)
    - Dept. of Emergency Management - Radiological Emergency Response Plan, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Dept. of Health - Shellfish condemnation, 1964-1994. (Box 8)
  - Accession 50533 (1937-2004, 15 cubic feet).
    Finding aid includes the the names of the agencies or boards included in each box. For file inventory for this accession, see: Detailed Folder Listing (50533).
    - Dept. of State Police, 1964-2000. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Employment Commission, 1983-1994. (Box 1)
    - State Milk Commission, 1972-2001. (Box 1)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1937-1996. (Box 2)
    - Auctioneers Board, 1984-1999. (Box 3)
    - Board for Branch Pilots, 1984-1999. (Box 3)
    - Board for Contractors, 1975-1999. (Box 3)
    - Board for Cosmetology, 1972-1999. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1986-1993. (Box 4)
    - Dept. of Health, 1995. (Box 4)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1956-1994. (Box 5)
    - Dept. of Health, 1965-2002. (Box 6)
    - Dept. of Health, 1977-2002. (Box 7)
    - Dept. of Health, 1971-2002. (Box 8)
    - Dept. of Health, 1958-1994. (Box 9)
    - Dept. of Health, 1972-2004. (Box 10)
    - Virginia Medical Care Facilities Certificate of Public Need - State Medical Facilities Plan (12 VAC 5-220), 1978-2994. (Box 11)
    - Board of Accountancy / Virginia Private Bond Regulations (18 VAC 5-20 - 13 VAC 5-190), 1977-2001. (Box 12)
    - Methods and Standards for Establishing Payment Rates for Long-Term Care - Patient Level Data System (12 VAC 25-40), 1980-2002. (Box 13)
    - State Education Assistance Authority / Public Participation Guidelines / Pertaining to Setting and Mesh Size of Gill Nets (8 VAC 25-10 - 4 VAC 20-751), 19. (Box 14)
    - Public Participation Guidelines / Hauling Permit Manual (18 VAC 55-10 - 24 VAC 30-110), 1974-2002. (Box 15)
  - Accession 51359 (1954-2012, 24 cubic feet).
    There is no detailed folder list for this accession.
    - Pesticide Control Board, 1991. (Box 1)
    - State Air Pollution Control Board, 1988-2003. (Box 1)
    - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 1971-2003. (Box 2)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1977-2001. (Box 3)
    - Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission, 1993-2000. (Box 3)
    - Commission on Local Government, 1980. (Box 3)
    - Board for Contractors, 1991-2003. (Box 3)
    - State Internal Auditor, 1995. (Box 3)
    - Real Estate Appraiser Board, 1990-2004. (Box 3)
    - Board for Asbestos, Lead and Home Inspectors, 1994-2000. (Box 4)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 1988-1996. (Box 4)
    - Dept. of General Services, 1989. (Box 4)
    - Dept. of Commerce, 1990. (Box 4)
    - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 1997-1999. (Box 5)
    - Board of Corrections, 1978-2000. (Box 5)
    - State Board of Juvenile Justice, 1978-1981. (Box 5)
    - Board of Accountancy, 1983-2003. (Box 6)
    - Dept. for the Aging, 1984-2002. (Box 6)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1975-2012. (Box 6)
    - Commercial Driver Training Schools, 1969-1990. (Box 7)
    - Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, 1970-2006. (Box 7)
    - Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development, 1977-1984. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Board, 2002. (Box 7)
    - Board of Social Work, 1987-2004. (Box 7)
    - Marine Resources Commission, 1980-2003. (Box 8)
    - Marine Resources Commission, 1984-2003. (Box 9)
    - Marine Resources Commission, 1988-2004. (Box 10)
    - Dept. of General Services, 1969-1994. (Box 11)
    - George Mason University, 1994-2000. (Box 11)
    - Dept. of Historic Resources, 1991-1994. (Box 11)
    - Dept. for the Blind and Vision Impaired, 1988-2002. (Box 12)
    - Dept. for the Visually Handicapped, 1984-1994. (Box 12)
    - Dept. for Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, 1993. (Box 12)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 1998-1999. (Box 12)
    - Board for Branch Pilots, 2002. (Box 12)
    - Cemetery Board, 2000. (Box 12)
    - Charitable Gaming Commission, 1996-1998. (Box 12)
    - Dept. of Fire Programs, 1986. (Box 12)
    - Dept. of Forestry, 1976-1994. (Box 12)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1971-2001. (Box 13)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1954-2003. (Box 14)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1975-2003. (Box 15)
    - Child Day Care Council, 1987-2002. (Box 16)
    - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance, 1988-2003. (Box 17)
    - Commission on the Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program, 1989. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Athletic Commission, 1966-2004. (Box 18)
    - Board for Audiology and Speech Language Pathology, 1973-2001. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Aviation Board, 1984-1992. (Box 18)
    - Virginia State Bar, 1991-1993. (Box 18)
    - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 1968-2003. (Box 18)
    - Virginia Employment Commission, 1993-2003. (Box 18)
    - State Board of Community Colleges (Policy manual revisions), 1993-2003. (Box 19)
    - Board for Geology, 1983-1999. (Box 19)
    - Regulation Certification Records - Various agencies, 1992-1994. (Box 20)
    - Regulation Certification Records - Various agencies, 1993-1994. (Box 21)
    - Regulation Certification Records - Various agencies, 1993-1995. (Box 22)
    - Regulation Certification Records - Various agencies, 1993-1994. (Box 23)
    - Regulation Certification Records - Various agencies, 1992-1995. (Box 24)
  - Accession 51557 (1957-2004, 4 cubic feet).
    Finding aid includes the the names of the agencies or boards included in each box. For file inventory for this accession, see: Detailed Folder Listing (51557).
    - Dept. of Criminal Justice Services, 1971-2004. (Box 1)
    - Dept. of Commerce, 1983-1992. (Box 2)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 1981. (Box 2)
    - State Board of Juvenile Justice, 1990-1995. (Box 2)
    - Dept. of Youth and Family Services, undated. (Box 2)
    - Dept. of Education, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1990. (Box 2)
    - Transportation Safety Board, 1981. (Box 2)
    - Virginia Workers' Compensation Commission, 1995-1996. (Box 2)
    - Industrial Commission of Virginia, 1985-1989. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1957-1993. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, 1984-2004. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Deaf and Hard of Hearing, 1989-1994. (Box 4)
    - Board of Dentistry, 2000-2003. (Box 4)
    - Design-Build Construction Management Review Board, 1997. (Box 4)
    - Board for Funeral Directors and Embalmers, 1972-2003. (Box 4)
  - Accession 51826 (1973-2016, 16 cubic feet).
    Finding aid includes the the names of the agencies or boards included in each box. For file inventory for this accession, see: Detailed Folder Listing (51826).
    - Dept. of Agriculture, 1992-2002. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Code Commission, 2016. (Box 2)
    - State Board of Elections, 2010-2014. (Box 2)
    - Office of the State Inspector General, 2015-2016. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Law, 1981-2015. (Box 3)
    - Commission on Local Government, 2006-2008. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Human Resource Management, 1990-2014. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of the Treasury, 1992-2008. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1985-2015. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1985-2015. (Box 4)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1986-2015. (Box 5)
    - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1980-2015. (Box 6)
    - Dept. of Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1985-1994. (Box 6)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1994-2014. (Box 7)
    - Marine Resources Commission, 1981-2015. (Box 7)
    - Board of Conservation and Recreation, 2008. (Box 8)
    - Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, 1980-2016. (Box 8)
    - Dept. of Forestry, 1989-2015. (Box 8)
    - Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries, 1979-2015. (Box 8)
    - Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries, 1973-2015. (Box 9)
    - Marine Resources Commission, 1984-2015. (Box 10)
    - Marine Resources Commission, 1989-2016. (Box 11)
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 1994-2013. (Box 12)
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 1984-2012. (Box 13)
    - Board on Conservation and Development of Public Beaches, 1982. (Box 13)
    - Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Board, 1989-2016. (Box 13)
    - Potomac River Fisheries Commission, 2016. (Box 13)
    - State Corporation Commission, 2001-2013. (Box 13)
    - Dept. of Juvenile Justice, 1997-2016. (Box 13)
    - Dept. of Corrections, 1997-2016. (Box 14)
    - Dept. of Criminal Justice Services, 1987-2015. (Box 14)
    - Dept. of Criminal Justice Services, 1994-2015. (Box 15)
    - Virginia Indigent Defense Commission, 1992. (Box 15)
    - Dept. of Juvenile Justice, 1997-2016. (Box 15)
    - Dept. of Juvenile Justice, 2004-2008. (Box 16)
    - Dept. of Forensic Science, 2006-2015. (Box 16)
    - Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, 1991-2010. (Box 16)
    - State Board of Education, 1994-2015. (Box 16)
  - Accession 51976 (1969-2016, 30 cubic feet).
    Finding aid includes the the names of the agencies or boards included in each box. For file inventory for this accession, see: Detailed Folder Listing (51976).
    - Dept. of Health, 1990-2015. (Box 1)
    - Dept. of Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, 2002-2016. (Box 1)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 2003-2014. (Box 1)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1973-2016. (Box 2)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 19. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 1978-2014. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Manufactured Housing Board, 1984-2012. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1984-2011. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1984-2015. (Box 5)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1985-2005. (Box 6)
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1978-2009. (Box 7)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 1973-2003. (Box 8)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1969-2016. (Box 9)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1988-2016. (Box 10)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1970-2016. (Box 11)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1982-2016. (Box 12)
    - Virginia State Bar, 1992-2016. (Box 12)
    - Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission, 2001. (Box 12)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1984-1999. (Box 13)
    - Safety and Health Codes Board, 1981-2015. (Box 14)
    - Safety and Health Codes Board, 1986-2016. (Box 15)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1988-1998. (Box 16)
    - Safety and Health Codes Board, 1978-2016. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Workers' Compensation Commission, 1991-2009. (Box 17)
    - Board of Historic Resources, 1991-2016. (Box 17)
    - Dept. of Historic Resources, 1994-2016. (Box 17)
    - Library of Virginia, 1970-2016. (Box 17)
    - Board of Accountancy, 2008-2013. (Box 18)
    - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2007-2016. (Box 18)
    - Board for Asbestos, Lead, and Home Inspectors, 2003-2015. (Box 19)
    - Auctioneers Board, 1995-2016. (Box 19)
    - Board for Audiology and Speech-Language Pathology, 2008-2016. (Box 19)
    - Board of Bar Examiners, 1993. (Box 19)
    - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2003-2016. (Box 19)
    - Board for Branch Pilots, 19f89-2012. (Box 19)
    - Cemetery Board, 2000-2016. (Box 19)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 1986-1996. (Box 20)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 1982-2000. (Box 21)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 1976-2000. (Box 22)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 1967-2002. (Box 23)
    - Common Interest Community Board, 2008-2016. (Box 24)
    - Board for Contractors, 1997-2016. (Box 24)
    - Board of Dentistry, 2008-2016. (Box 24)
    - Fair Housing Board, 2005-2008. (Box 24)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 1989-2013. (Box 25)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 1996-2009. (Box 26)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 1997-2009. (Box 27)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1988-2013. (Box 28)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1998-2002. (Box 29)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1990-1998. (Box 30)
  - Accession 52018 (1952-2017, 47 cubic feet).
    Finding aid includes the the names of the agencies or boards included in each box. For file inventory for this accession, see: Detailed Folder Listing (52018).
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1993-2017. (Box 1)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1995-2016. (Box 2)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1991-2017. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1985-2016. (Box 4)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 2000-2015. (Box 5)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 2003-2016. (Box 6)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1991-1994. (Box 7)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1988-1992. (Box 8)
    - Board of Funeral Directors and Embalmers, 1999-2015. (Box 9)
    - Board of Health Professions, 1994-2008. (Box 9)
    - Dept. of Health Professions, 1997-2014. (Box 9)
    - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, 1995-2012. (Box 9)
    - Board of Medicine, 1998-2008. (Box 9)
    - Board of Medicine, 1994-2017. (Box 10)
    - Board of Medicine, 2007-2016. (Box 11)
    - Board of Nursing, 1992-2016. (Box 11)
    - Dept. of Education, 1968-2002. (Box 12)
    - Dept. of Education, 1980-2002. (Box 13)
    - Dept. of Education, 1959-2009. (Box 14)
    - Board of Optometry, 2003-2015. (Box 15)
    - Board of Pharmacy, 1993-2016. (Box 15)
    - Board of Counseling, 1977-2002. (Box 16)
    - Dept. of Education, 1974. (Box 16)
    - Library of Virginia, 1972-2008. (Box 16)
    - Dept. of Commerce, 1952-1988. (Box 16)
    - Board of Pharmacy, 1990-2016. (Box 17)
    - Board of Physical Therapy, 2000-2015. (Box 17)
    - Board of Counseling, 1998-2016. (Box 17)
    - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1993-2015. (Box 18)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 1991-1999. (Box 19)
    - Dept. of Government Employment and Training, 1983-1998. (Box 19)
    - Dept. of the Treasury, 1985-2008. (Box 19)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 1995-2016. (Box 20)
    - Board of Psychology, 1997-2016. (Box 20)
    - Real Estate Appraiser Board, 1995-2016. (Box 20)
  - Accession 52837 (1953-2016, 33 cubic feet).
    Finding aid includes the the names of the agencies or boards included in each box. For file inventory for this accession, see: Detailed Folder Listing (52837).
    - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy, 1985-2013. (Box 1)
    - Potomac River Fisheries Commission, 2000-2016. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Board, 1995-2012. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Board, 1989-2013. (Box 2)
    - State Corporation Commission, 2007-2011. (Box 2)
    - Dept./Board of Correctional Education, 1997. (Box 2)
    - Dept. of Corrections, 1997-2011. (Box 2)
    - Dept. of Criminal Justice Services, 1989-2015. (Box 2)
    - Dept. of Criminal Justice Services, 2000-2015. (Box 3)
    - Dept./Board of Juvenile Justice, 1991-2015. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Forensic Science, 2006-2008. (Box 3)
    - Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, 2004-2008. (Box 3)
    - State Board of Education, 1980-2016. (Box 4)
    - George Mason University, 2010-2012. (Box 4)
    - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, 1989-2015. (Box 4)
    - Longwood University, 1995. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1995-2013. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1994-2013. (Box 5)
    - College of William and Mary, 1994. (Box 5)
    - State Air Pollution Control Board, 1985-2015. (Box 5)
    - State Air Pollution Control Board, 1985-2015. (Box 6)
    - State Air Pollution Control Board, 1997-2012. (Box 7)
    - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Board, 2002-2012. (Box 7)
    - Dept. of Environmental Quality, 2009-2013. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Waste Management Board, 1986-2014. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Waste Management Board, 1988-2015. (Box 8)
    - State Water Control Board, 1996-2013. (Box 9)
    - State Water Control Board, 1976-2013. (Box 10)
    - State Water Control Board, 2005-2008. (Box 11)
    - State Water Control Board, 1989-2014. (Box 12)
    - State Water Control Board, 1970-1982. (Box 13)
    - Virginia Soil and Water Conservation Board, 1974-2003. (Box 14)
    - Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, 1996. (Box 14)
    - State Corporation Commission, 1992-2012. (Box 15)
    - Virginia Lottery Board, 2003-2012. (Box 15)
    - Virginia Racing Commission, 1990-2013. (Box 15)
    - Charitable Gaming Board, 2006-2012. (Box 15)
    - Dept. of Health, 1983-2016. (Box 16)
    - Dept. of Health, 1982-2016. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Health Planning Board, 1990-2014. (Box 17)
    - Dept. of Behavioral Health and Developmentatl Services, 1994-2016. (Box 17)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 1953-2008. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Manufactured Housing Board, 2006. (Box 17)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1989-2014. (Box 17)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 1975-2007. (Box 18)
    - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 2003-2008. (Box 19)
    - State Corporation Commission - Bureau of Insurance, 1958-2014. (Box 20)
    - Virginia State Bar, 1990-2016. (Box 20)
    - Virginia Employment Commission, 2002-2011. (Box 21)
    - Dept. of Labor and Industry, 1979-1999. (Box 21)
    - Apprenticeship Council, 1992-2014. (Box 21)
    - Safety and Health Codes Board, 1981-2016. (Box 21)
    - Virginia Workers' Compensation Commission, 2008-2009. (Box 21)
    - Board of Historic Resources, 2008. (Box 21)
    - Dept. of Historic Resources, 2006-2008. (Box 21)
    - Library of Virginia, 1986-2016. (Box 21)
    - Board of Accountancy, 2001-2010. (Box 22)
    - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers, and Landscape Architects, 2000-2009. (Box 22)
    - Board for Asbestos, Lead, and Home Inspectors, 2002-2015. (Box 22)
    - Auctioneers Board, 2002-2009. (Box 22)
    - Board for Audiology and Speech-Language Pathology, 1998-2016. (Box 23)
    - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2002-2016. (Box 23)
    - Board for Branch Pilots, 2001-2008. (Box 23)
    - Cemetery Board, 2000-2014. (Box 23)
    - Common Interest Community Board, 2008-2015. (Box 24)
    - Board for Contractors, 1999-2015. (Box 24)
    - Board of Dentistry, 1987-2015. (Box 24)
    - Board of Dentistry, 1998-2006. (Box 25)
    - Fair Housing Board, 2004-2005. (Box 25)
    - Board for Funeral Directors and Embalmers, 1991-2015. (Box 25)
    - Board for Geology, 2004-2012. (Box 25)
    - Board of Health Professions, 1996-2015. (Box 25)
    - Dept. of Health Professions, 2003-2008. (Box 25)
    - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, 2001-2017. (Box 25)
    - Board of Medicine, 1991-2015. (Box 25)
    - Board of Medicine, 1992-2012. (Box 26)
    - Board of Nursing, 1995-2017. (Box 26)
    - Board of Nursing, 2004-2015. (Box 27)
    - Board of Long-Term Care Administrators, 2004-2010. (Box 27)
    - Board for Opticians, 2001-2012. (Box 27)
    - Board of Optometry, 2003-2016. (Box 27)
    - Board of Pharmacy, 1988-2016. (Box 27)
    - Board of Physical Therapy, 2002-2018. (Box 28)
    - Board of Counseling, 1997-2010. (Box 28)
    - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2003-2008. (Box 28)
    - Board of Psychology, 2009-2014. (Box 28)
    - Real Estate Appraiser Board, 2003-2013. (Box 28)
    - Real Estate Board, 1991. (Box 28)
    - Board of Social Work, 1986-2013. (Box 28)
    - Board for Soil Scientists, Wetland Professionals, and Geologists, 2002-2010. (Box 29)
    - Board of Veterinary Medicine, 2005-2013. (Box 29)
    - Board for Waste Management Facility Operators, 2004-2011. (Box 29)
    - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage System Professionals, 2004-2008. (Box 29)
    - State Corporation Commission, 2000-2012. (Box 29)
    - Dept. for the Aging, 2009-2012. (Box 30)